<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Studio Nugget Devlog</title>
    <link>https://studionugget.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Studio Nugget Devlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 22:32:47 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://studionugget.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Operation Tempest – Devlog #3</title>
      <link>https://studionugget.com/posts/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 22:32:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studionugget.com/posts/3/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jacob and I’m here to give a final update before we complete the prototype for Operation: Tempest. In the last devlog I talked about the future of the game. I’m happy to report that we’re on track to have a prototype up and running sometime before the end of the month! We have been working hard on a lot of stuff behind the scenes, as much of the design for the beginning elements of the game have already been completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operation Tempest – Devlog #2</title>
      <link>https://studionugget.com/posts/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 21:23:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studionugget.com/posts/2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to the second devlog for Studio Nugget’s upcoming game, (working title) Operation Tempest!
My name is Jacob and I’m here to give an update that is long overdue. This time I would like to talk about some of the methods we have used in making and designing the game, what we have been focusing on in recent months, and what the future of Operation Tempest looks like.
Billy and Patrick, our programmers and artists, have been hard at work on creating the key features on both the back end and front end of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operation Tempest – Devlog #1</title>
      <link>https://studionugget.com/posts/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studionugget.com/posts/1/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to the first devlog post for Studio Nugget’s first game, (working title) Operation Tempest!
My name is Jacob and I am the project lead for Operation Tempest. I’m writing this first of many (sporadic) blog posts to document our project’s journey from the beginning stages to a fully developed game. All of us here at Studio Nugget are now working on this game full time and we’re very excited to begin sharing information about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://studionugget.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://studionugget.com/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>